hungryforapps.com 2018-12-23

# Privacy Policy | SharewareOnSale

Just like any other website on the internet, we run statistical packages on SharewareOnSale.com. These packages track things like what is the most popular post, how many people visited SharewareOnSale.com on a certain day, how many people downloaded a certain software, etc. Any information collected by these statistical packages is strictly on how users interact with SharewareOnSale.com and our related services. All data is only used for analysis to improve SharewareOnSale.com and our related services (e.g. figure out which topics people are interested in). Information from these statistical packages is never sold, traded, or given away in such a way that may lead to your personal identification. All information from these statistical packages is used in an aggregated manner to benefit SharewareOnSale.com and our related services. If you would like to know exactly what information these statistical plugins are collecting you can check them out for yourself: [Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics/).

We use WooCommerce to power our website and a record is kept of every download you get from us, including the information you provide to us (e.g., email). These records are to improve or benefit SharewareOnSale.com and our services; we don’t share, sell, or give this information to third-parties in such a way that may lead to your personal identification (e.g., we don’t give your email to third-parties). Third-parties is everyone that:

  * Is not part of our company, Azadi Network LLC
  * Is not part of the company (e.g., developer of the software being promoted) that has partnered with us to promote the offer in question

The company (e.g., developer of the software being promoted) that has partnered with us to promote the offer in question may have access to the information you provide to us (e.g., email). The company (e.g., developer of the software being promoted) that has partnered with us may contact you; for example, to solicit feedback or to provide help or to introduce you to their other products. The company (e.g., developer of the software being promoted) that has partnered with us has explicitly agreed to protect your privacy and not share or sell your information outside their company. You should be able to unsubscribe from their emails if you don’t want them. If they don’t let you unsubscribe, please [contact us](https://sharewareonsale.com/need-help) and let us know so we can lay the smackdown on them.

If demanded by law and through appropriate legal channels, we will share your information with law enforcement. We are headquartered in the United States and are thus subject to American law. (I apologize for our ~~clown-in-chief~~ current president.)

Outside of the statistical and WooCommerce usage mentioned above, ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION (such as country, name, e-mail address, and IP address) SENT TO US IS ON YOUR OWN ACCORD, SUCH AS WHEN YOU DOWNLOAD A PRODUCT, E-MAIL US, POST A COMMENT, MAKE A FORUM POST, SIGNUP FOR EMAIL NOTIFICATIONS, OR REGISTER ON SHAREWAREONSALE.COM. YOU MAY RECEIVE E-MAILS FROM US (THESE E-MAILS WILL NOT BE SPAM BUT MAY CONTAIN ADVERTISEMENTS); also if the situation demands it, your IP may be compared to that of others to determine if you are a spammer or a repeat offender under a different name. IF YOU DO NOT FEEL COMFORTABLE GIVING OUT YOUR REAL NAME AND E-MAIL ADDRESS THEN DON’T USE OUR WEBSITE. The Internet was not designed to be a private place. IF PRIVACY IS A BIG ISSUE, USE A PROXY, OR OTHER TECHNIQUES, TO HIDE YOUR IP ADDRESS WHENEVER YOU SURF THE INTERNET. Just be careful when using proxies, because many proxies are not anonymous and can in fact hurt you, in terms of privacy and collecting your personal information, more than not using a proxy. To learn more about what an IP address is, read [Wikipedia](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ip_address).

For non-free (aka paid) products and downloads on SharewareOnSale.com, you may be sent directly to a developer’s or partner’s website/shopping cart to make your purchase or your purchase may be processed internally by our own checkout process. All payments via the website/checkout system of developers and partners adhere to their own terms and conditions and privacy policies. All payments made on SharewareOnSale.com via our internal system are processed by third-party payment processing vendors: PayPal and Stripe. All your financial information is stored on their servers and they are responsible for its security.

To earn some revenue to support the efforts of SharewareOnSale.com, we run ads. One of our major ad platforms is Google AdSense ads. Google, and Google’s advertising partners, use special tricks to make sure they are doing good advertising. Here is the official legal blurb:

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

What Google does is out of our control. Sue them if you don’t like it.

By using SharewareOnSale.com we assume you accept everything mentioned here. If you don’t, leave now. We hate to see you go. =(

 _ _We reserve the right to change or modify the  Privacy Statement with no prior notice.__
